[Music]
[音乐]
this is nick with logosbynic.com and in
我是logosbynic.com的尼克
this tutorial i'll be demonstrating how
在本教程中，我将演示
you can create this vintage style logo
您可以创建这个复古风格的徽标
design
设计
using inkscape in order to follow along
使用Inkscape以跟随
with this tutorial though you will need
但在本教程中，您将需要
to download and install the font that i
下载并安装我所使用的字体
used for the word design here it's
在这里用来表示设计这个词
called festival bedai
叫节日贝代
i'll have a link in the description of
我会在描述中有一个链接
the video so go ahead and download and
因此，请继续下载并下载视频
install that font before
在安装该字体之前
launching inkscape and then we'll be
推出Inkscape，然后我们将
good to go before we get started though
不过，在我们开始之前可以走了
if you'd like to learn more about how
如果您想了解更多有关如何
inkscape works be sure to check out my
Inkscape作品一定要查看我的
inkscape master class
Inkscape大师班
it's a collection of over 60 videos
这是60多个视频的集合
where i go through every single tool and
在那里我检查了每一个工具和
feature in inkscape
Inkscape中的功能
and i explain what it is and i
我解释了它是什么，然后我
demonstrate how it works i'll have some
演示一下它是如何工作的，我要一些
information about that
关于这方面的信息
in the description of the video if you
在视频描述中，如果您
want to check that out
想去看看吗？
so we'll go ahead and get started here
所以我们继续，从这里开始
in inkscape the first thing i want to do
在Inkscape中，我想做的第一件事
is just set up the document i want to
就是设置我想要的文档
come up here to where it says view
到上面写着风景的地方来
make sure you have custom selected let's
确保您已经选择了定制，让我们
go to zoom let's zoom in at one to one
转到ZOOM让我们以一比一的速度放大
and then i'm going to turn off snapping
然后我将关闭捕捉
up here in the top left corner and then
在这里的左上角，然后
i'm going to open
我要去开门了
up the um the document properties menu
打开这个文档属性菜单
to get rid of this page border and
若要消除此页面边框并
change the unit of measurement here so
更改此处的测量单位，以便
i'll go to
我要去
file document properties and it should
对文档属性进行归档，它应该
open up over here on the side
打开这边的门
display units i'm going to change that
显示单位我要更改一下
to pixels and i'm going to
到像素，我要
turn off the visibility of the page
关闭页面的可见性
border which is over here
在这里的边界
so now we can close out of document
所以现在我们可以关闭文档了
properties let's open up the fill and
属性，让我们打开填充并
stroke menu which is over here the edit
笔划菜单，位于此处的编辑
objects colors gradients and stroke menu
对象、颜色、渐变和笔触菜单
if you click on that
如果你点击它
or a keyboard shortcut you can just
或者键盘快捷键，您只需
press ctrl shift and f and that'll open
按Ctrl、Shift和f，系统将打开
it as well
它也是如此
so the first thing i'm going to do is
所以我要做的第一件事是
create the text so let's grab the text
创建文本，让我们抓取文本
tool
工具
which is if i could find it it should be
也就是说，如果我能找到它，它应该是
over here i'm used to using these
在这里，我习惯于使用这些
keyboard shortcuts so i sometimes get
键盘快捷键，所以我有时会得到
lost over here in the sidebar so
在侧边栏里迷路了，所以
let me just type in design as i did for
让我像输入设计一样输入设计
the thumbnail here if you notice i have
这里的缩略图如果你注意到我有
the word design as the
设计这个词就像
primary text i'm going to change the
主文本我要更改
font of that
该字体的字体
i'm going to go to text text and font
我要转到文本文本和字体
and i'm going to look for the font that
我要寻找的字体是
i installed called festival badaya
我安装了一个叫节日巴达亚的
click apply and there you go there you
单击Apply(应用)，即可转到此处
have the text now we can close out of
现在我们可以关闭文本了吗
the text menu
文本菜单
i'm going to grab the select tool and
我要抓起选择工具，
i'm going to scale this up and i'm just
我要把它放大，我只是
going to hold ctrl while i do that to
在我执行此操作时按住Ctrl键
make sure it locks the proportions like
确保它锁定的比例如下
that
那
and now what i want to do is convert
现在我想要做的是把
this to a path and ungroup it so i'll go
这是一条路径，然后解组，这样我就可以走了
to path
至路径
object to path and then go to object
对象到路径，然后转到对象
and we're looking for ungroup and i'm
我们正在寻找解组，而我是
going to bring down the opacity of this
我要把这个的不透明性降下来
roughly in half now you have to have the
大约一半，现在你必须要有
fill and stroke menu open in order to do
打开填充和描边菜单以执行以下操作
this so make sure you have that opened
所以一定要把它打开
i'm going to bring down the opacity
我要把不透明度降下来
roughly in half and now i want to move
大概对半，现在我想搬家
these letters a little closer together
这些字母靠得更近一些
so i'm going to hold
所以我要等一下
ctrl i'm going to zoom in by holding
按住Ctrl键进行放大
ctrl and rolling up the mouse wheel
按住Ctrl键并滚动鼠标滚轮
click off of the graphic to deselect
单击图形以取消选择
everything and i'm going to take this
所有的东西，我要拿着这个
letter d and i'm just going to move this
字母d和我要把这个
closer but i'm going to hold ctrl while
更近了，但我要按住Ctrl键
i do that to lock it onto the horizontal
我这样做是为了把它锁在水平线上
axis like that
像这样的轴线
and then i'm going to hold shift and
然后我要按住班次
click on the letter e so i have both of
点击字母e，这样我就有了这两个
these letters selected
选定的这些字母
hold ctrl move this closer now i
按住Ctrl键，现在把这个移近一点
understand that the letter s
明白S这封信
here is overlapping with the letters but
这里与字母重叠，但
that's okay in fact that's kind of the
没关系，事实上，这是一种
point of the design i'm going to be
我要做的设计要点是
incorporating that into the design here
把它融入到这里的设计中
as you can see so i'm going to hold
如你所见，我会坚持下去
shift click on the letter s so we have
按住Shift键点击字母S，这样我们就有了
all three of these letters selected
这三个字母全部选中
and to move your view around like this
像这样移动你的视线
to move the page you can just press down
要移动页面，只需按下即可
the mouse wheel and move the mouse
鼠标滚轮并移动鼠标
let me move these over while holding
让我拿着的时候把这些搬过去
control to lock the proportions
控件来锁定比例。
and then just do the same thing for the
然后只需对
rest of the word just go ahead and bring
剩下的话就去吧，带上
these letters in
这些字母在
like that and now i will press one on
就像这样，现在我要按下一个
the keyboard to zoom back out to 100
缩小到100的键盘
so now what i'm going to do is i'm going
所以现在我要做的是我要去
to create this shape in the background
要在背景中创建此形状
here this emblem so let me
给你这个徽章让我
go back into inkscape and i'm going to
回到Inkscape，我要
grab the squares and rectangles tool
抓取正方形和矩形工具
which is over here
它就在这里
and i'm going to click and drag like
我要点击并拖动，就像
this to create a nice vertical rectangle
这样可以创建一个漂亮的垂直矩形
going through the word like that you
就像你说的那样
want to make sure you have sharp corners
想要确保你有锋利的拐角
up here if your if your corners are
如果你，如果你的角落是
rounded just go ahead and click this
四舍五入只需继续并单击此按钮
corner button up here to make the
角按钮在这里，以使
corners sharp
棱角锐利
and now i will grab these circles and
现在我要抓住这些圆圈
ellipses tool and i will click and drag
省略号工具和我将点击并拖动
to create any lips going through that
创造出任何嘴唇都穿过那个
rectangle kind of like that
长方形有点像那样
now if you notice what i'm doing here
现在如果你注意到我在这里做什么
i'm going to take the intersecting area
我要去交叉区域
between those two shapes
在这两个形状之间
in order to create this shape right here
为了在这里创建这个形状
so to do that
所以要做到这一点
first let me make sure i have them
首先，让我确认一下我有没有
aligned i'm going to grab the select
对齐了，我要去拿精选
tool i'm going to hold shift and click
工具我要按住Shift键并单击
on the rectangle so i have them both
在长方形上，所以我两个都有
selected
已选择
and then i'll open up the align and
然后我会打开Align和
distribute menu which is
分发菜单，它是
over here or you can press ctrl shift
在这里，或者你可以按ctrl Shift键
and a
以及一个
and i want to have the relative set to
我想要把这个亲戚设置成
last selected
上次选择的时间
and i'm going to center it up on the
我将把它集中在
vertical axis and then i'll go to
垂直轴，然后我将转到
path intersection and there we go now we
小路交叉口，我们现在就去吧
have that
有那个吗？
shape now don't worry about this shape
形状现在不用担心这个形状
being too big or too small we're going
无论是太大还是太小，我们都要去
to change that later on
为了在以后改变这一点
so i'm going to place this right about
所以我要把这个放在
here in fact what i want to do is i want
事实上，我想做的是我想
to click and drag over the text
在文本上单击并拖动的步骤
right here to select the text items
就在这里选择文本项
click and drag over just the text not
仅在文本注释上单击并拖动
the whole
整个
shape just the text itself and go to
只调整文本本身的形状并转到
object
对象
group and then i want to click and drag
分组，然后我想要单击并拖动
over everything
压倒一切
just to make sure i have this aligned
只是为了确保我把这个对准
vertically i'm going to click on uh
在垂直方向上，我将点击
center on vertical axis right there and
在垂直轴上居中，在那里
then click off to deselect
然后单击关闭以取消选择
everything now what i could do is i
现在我能做的一切就是我
could take this i'm going to hold ctrl
可以拿着这个吗？我要按住Ctrl键
and shift and either scale it up or
和Shift，并将其扩展或
scale it down whatever you want to do
无论你想做什么，都要缩小规模
whatever
管它呢
whatever you need to do to make it fit
无论你需要做什么来使它合身
the design better i like how this looks
这个设计更好我喜欢这个的样子
right about here
就在这里
i'm going to grab the edit paths by
我将通过以下方式获取编辑路径
nodes tool i'm going to click and drag
我要单击并拖动的节点工具
over these top nodes right here and then
在这些顶层节点上不时出现
just bring them down
把他们拉下来就行了
by holding ctrl and just click and
通过按住Ctrl键并单击并
dragging them down like that
像这样把他们拖下水
there we go now let's go back to the
好了，现在让我们回到
select tool let's make this thing into
选择工具让我们把这件事变成
an outline rather than a solid fill so
轮廓而不是实心填充，因此
let's remove the fill color by clicking
让我们通过单击删除填充颜色
on this little red x down here in the
在下面这个红色的小x上
bottom left corner
左下角
and then give this a black stroke by
然后给这个画一个黑色的笔划
holding shift and clicking on the color
按住Shift键并单击颜色
black over there
那边是黑色的
now the thickness of this will vary uh
现在这个厚度会有所不同呢
you can change that by coming over here
你可以通过来到这里来改变这一点
to the fill and stroke menu
添加到填充和描边菜单
i'm going to tap i'm going to click on
我要点击，我要点击
stroke style
笔划样式
and i want this to be about 15 looks
我希望这是15个造型
pretty good
挺不错的
now whatever it is that you make the
现在不管你做的是什么
thickness of your stroke be
你笔划的粗细是
make sure you make a mental note of what
一定要在脑海中记下什么
that is because we're going to we're
那是因为我们要去我们要
going to need that number in just a
在接下来的一段时间里需要这个数字
minute so
分钟，所以
15 is for this first one right here now
15美元就是现在这里的第一个
we'll go to
我们将前往
path stroke to path path
路径笔划到路径路径
uh break apart and then go to
嗯，分开，然后去
path difference
路径差
oops that was a mistake let me undo that
哦，那是个错误，让我来撤销吧
edit undo difference
编辑撤消差异
and then click off of it to deselect
然后将其关闭以取消选择
everything and then take this larger
所有东西，然后把这个放大一点
shape right here
形状就在这里
send that to the back by pressing this
按这个，把那个送到后面去
button over here that says lower
这里的按钮，上面写着更低
selection to the bottom
选择到底部
and then hold shift and click on the
然后按住Shift键并单击
smaller shape right there and go to
小一点的形状，然后转到
path difference so that you end up with
路径差异，所以你最终会得到
this shape right here that is a
这个形状在这里，是一个
path and not a stroke now let's
路径，而不是中风，现在让我们
duplicate this let's press ctrl d on the
复制这个，让我们按下ctrl d键
keyboard to make a duplicate copy of
要复制的键盘
this
这
go to path uh break apart
去小路上，嗯，分开
and we'll go to path union
我们会去PATH联盟
and now what i'm going to do is i'm
现在我要做的是
going to make this red and i'm going to
我要把它变成红色，我要
give this a red outline by holding shift
按住Shift键显示红色轮廓
and clicking on the color red like that
然后像这样点击红色
and i'm going to make this outline a
我要把这个提纲变成一个
little bigger i'm going to make this
我要把这个做得更大一点
maybe
也许吧
10. this is going to represent the space
10.这将代表空间
between the two borders here if you
在这两个边界之间，如果你
notice we made this first border already
请注意，我们已经创建了第一个边框
now we're going to make this second
现在我们要把这一秒
border this red object is going to
此红色对象的边框将
represent the space between those two
表示这两者之间的空格
borders
边框
so let me go back in there and finish
所以让我回去把话说完
this up let me change this make this a
这让我把它改成一个
little bigger
稍大一点
you hold the plus icon to make that
按住加号图标即可实现这一点
bigger like that
像那样大一点
that's looking pretty good now when
现在看起来很不错，当
you're doing this i probably should have
你在做这件事我可能应该这么做
noted over here where it says join make
注意到这里写着加入Make
sure you have a square join you don't
当然，你有一个方形连接，你不是吗？
want a rounded join like that you want
我想要一个你想要的圆角连接
it to be nice and square so you get
它应该是正方形的，这样你就可以
those square corners
那些正方形的角落
maybe i'll make that a little bit bigger
也许我会把它做大一点
and i'll do this again i'll go to
我会再做一次，我会去
path stroke to path path
路径笔划到路径路径
break apart if i can find it there it is
如果我能找到的话就散开吧
go to object ungroup and then go to
转到对象，取消分组，然后转到
path union now we're going to do this
路径联盟现在我们要做这件事
one more time i'm going to add a smaller
再说一次，我要添加一个较小的
stroke over here now this stroke right
划过来，现在这划向右
here was 15 pixels i'm going to make
这是我要制作的15个像素
this one a little bit smaller so i'm
这个稍微小了一点，所以我
going to hold shift and click on the
按住Shift键并单击
color black to give that an outline
把它涂成黑色，给它一个轮廓
let's click the red x to get rid of the
让我们单击红色的x以去掉
red fill and i'm going to make this
红色的填充物，我要做这个
something smaller than 15. maybe
小于15的，也许吧
something like 10.
大概10个左右。
that right there looks pretty good now
就在那里，现在看起来很不错
again we want to make sure we have
再次重申，我们希望确保我们拥有
squared
平方
a square join a squared cap like that
一个正方形把一个正方形的帽子连在一起
and i'd say that's looking pretty good
我要说的是这看起来很不错
right here now again you want to make a
现在，你又想要做一次
mental note of this so for this one i
记住这一点，所以对于这一次，我
used 15 for this one i used 10.
这次我用了15美元，我用了10美元。
let's go to path stroke to path and
让我们转到路径笔划到路径和
there we go
好了，我们走吧
now we can click off of that to deselect
现在，我们可以单击该选项以取消选择
everything so let's start working on
所有的一切，让我们开始工作吧
these little um
这些小小的嗯
horizontal bars going across the design
横跨设计的单杠
right here we'll do that next
就在这里，我们接下来要做的是
to do that what i'm going to do is i'm
为了做到这一点，我要做的是
going to grab the squares and rectangles
去抓取正方形和长方形
tool
工具
i'm going to click and drag to create a
我要单击并拖动以创建一个
rectangle going through the design right
穿过设计右侧的矩形
here
这里
and i want to get rid of that outline
我想摆脱那个提纲
i'm going to hold shift and click on the
我要按住Shift键并单击
red
红色
x and i'm just going to give that a
X，我要给它一个
black fill by clicking on black right
通过单击黑色右侧进行黑色填充
there
那里
and this is where we're going to have to
这就是我们要做的
remember this number that we used we
还记得我们用过的这个数字吗
want to make the height of this the same
我想让它的高度相同
thickness of this border right here so
这条边界的厚度就在这里
that it's consistent all the way through
它自始至终都是一致的
the design
设计
so let me grab the select tool let me
所以让我拿起选择工具让我
change the height of this well first let
先把这口井的高度改一下
me change the pixels
我要更改像素
let me change this to pixels change the
让我将其更改为像素更改
height of this to 15.
把这个高度调到15。
there we go move this over here a little
好了，我们要把这个移到这里来一点
closer to the word
更接近字面意思
maybe make this a little wider you can
也许你可以把这个弄宽一点
go ahead and adjust the size of this as
继续并将此文件的大小调整为
needed
需要
and then i just want to make sure that
然后我只想确保
this is aligned on the
这是在
vertical axis here so i'm going to hold
垂直轴在这里，所以我要拿着
shift click on the emblem behind it
按住Shift键并单击其后面的徽章
come back up here to the line distribute
回到这里来排好队
menu and make sure you have it centered
菜单，并确保将其居中
on the vertical axis like that
在这样的垂直轴上
and now click off of the deselect
现在，单击取消选择
everything and what i'm going to do now
所有的事情和我现在要做的
is i'm going to take this
我要拿着这个
shape right here and duplicate that by
就在这里塑造，然后复制它
pressing ctrl d
按Ctrl d键
hold ctrl move this up like this and
按住Ctrl键，像这样向上移动然后
again we're holding ctrl and clicking
我们再次按住Ctrl键并单击
and dragging to lock it onto the axis
并拖动以将其锁定到轴上
like that so it doesn't go
就像这样，所以它不会
off off center and i want to make the
偏离了中心，我想要参加
height of this the same as the thickness
这个高度和厚度一样
of this border so i used 10 pixels for
所以我用了10个像素
that one so i'll make this one 10 pixels
那个，所以我把这个设为10个像素
high
高
and there you go now i'm just going to
现在你走了，我要去
zoom in let me just zoom in a little bit
放大，让我稍微放大一点
whoops and i just want to make sure that
哎呀，我只是想确保
the spacing between these two lines
这两条线之间的间距
is about equal to the spacing between
大约等于之间的间距
those two lines if you want you can be
这两句话，如果你愿意，你可以
meticulous with this and measurement
一丝不苟地做这件事和测量
measure it if you want i'm just gonna
量一量，如果你想的话，我只是要
i'm just gonna leave it right about
我就把它留在这里吧
there i think that looks close enough
我觉得这看起来已经够近了
and then i want to take this and just
然后我想拿着这个，然后
move this in a little bit take this
把这个往前移一点，拿着这个
arrow move that in
箭头将其移入
take that arrow move that in like that
拿着那个箭头，像这样移进去
and then hold shift click on the
然后按住Shift键单击
original design behind it
它背后的原始设计
and then just make sure you have that
然后，只要确保你有这个
centered like that now we can click off
像这样居中，现在我们可以点击
of the graphic to deselect everything
以取消选择所有内容
let me press one on the keyboard to zoom
让我按键盘上的一键进行缩放
back out to 100
退回到100
and now i'm going to click and drag over
现在我要点击并拖动到
just those two rectangles right there
就那两个长方形
that we just
我们只是
created and i want to duplicate them
已创建，我想复制它们
i'll press ctrl d
我会按Ctrl d键
hold ctrl move these ones down here
按住Ctrl键将这些移动到这里
and i just want to flip them vertically
我只想垂直翻转它们
i could you can click on this button up
我可以，你可以向上点击这个按钮
here that says flip selected objects
此处显示翻转选定对象
vertically what i like to do is just
垂直来说，我喜欢做的就是
press the letter v
按字母v
on the keyboard much easier and once
在键盘上轻松得多，而且只需一次
you've done that you can click off of
你已经做了，你可以点击
that
那
okay so if you notice what we have here
好的，如果你注意到我们这里有什么
we have the structure of the design in
我们有这个设计的结构在
place
地点
now we just have to go through and uh
现在我们只需要通过和呃
fix some of the spacing issues or uh
解决一些间距问题，或者呃
finish up what we were doing here as far
把我们在这里做的事做完
as the spacing goes let me click on the
随着空格的增加，让我点击
word right here and then ungroup those
就在这里，然后解开那些
letters i'll go to object
我要去反对的信
ungroup because we previously had those
取消分组，因为我们之前有
letters grouped together let me click
组合在一起的字母让我点击
off that to deselect everything
关闭该选项以取消选择所有内容
and now i want to delete out the area of
现在我想删除这一区域
the emblem in the background where these
背景中的徽章，这些
words are so let me zoom in a little bit
文字是如此的让我放大一点
let me grab the squares and rectangles
我来拿正方形和长方形
tool i'm going to create a rectangle
工具，我要创建一个矩形
going over the word like that i'm going
像那样复习单词，我要去
to make this red so i can see it against
把它染成红色，这样我就能看到它了
everything else
其他的一切
and if you notice over here i have the
如果你注意到这里，我有一个
rectangle let me grab the select tool
矩形，让我抓起选择工具
i have the rectangle going through this
我让长方形穿过了这个
bar right here at the at the top and i
酒吧就在顶端，而我
have it going through this bar
让它穿过这个酒吧
oops i have it going through this bar
哦，我让它穿过了这个酒吧
down here at the bottom
就在这下面的底部
and now what i want to do is duplicate
现在我想要做的是复制
that by pressing ctrl d
通过按Ctrl d键
hold shift click on this shape go to
按住Shift键单击此形状转到
path
路径
difference then take this red shape hold
不同的是，拿这个红色的形状
shift click on this object out here and
按住Shift键单击此处的此对象，然后
go to
去
path difference
路径差
let me try that again path difference
让我再试一次路径差异
there we go
好了，我们走吧
and now i just want to delete out the
现在我只想删除
areas of this bar up here so let me grab
这个酒吧的区域在上面，让我拿一下
the rectangles and squares tool again
矩形和正方形工具再次出现
create a rectangle going through here
创建一个穿过此处的矩形
like this
就像这样
grab the select tool hold shift click on
抓住选择工具按住Shift键并单击
that object to go to path
要转到路径的对象
difference we'll do that one more time
不同的是，我们会再做一次
come down here to this one
到这里来，到这里来
so that it looks the same on the bottom
所以它在底部看起来是一样的
as it does on the top
就像它在顶部做的那样
hold shift click on that go to path
按住Shift键单击转到路径
i don't know why that's not working half
我不知道为什么这不管用一半
the time but there we go now it's
时间，但我们现在去，它是
working
工作中
okay so um oh you know what i made a
好的，那么，哦，你知道我做了什么吗
mistake here let me just edit that
这里有个错误，让我来编辑一下
i should have moved that in a little
我应该把它移近一点的
more there we go
我们再来一次
okay now to do that if you need to do
好的，如果你需要的话，现在就去做
what i just did there you just grab the
我刚才在那里做的，你只要抓住
nodes tool click and drag over those two
结点工具在这两个结点上单击并拖动
nodes you can just move them in and out
节点，您只需将它们移入移出即可
like that
就像这样
you can hold ctrl to lock it onto the
您可以按住Ctrl键将其锁定到
horizontal axis
水平轴
there we go all right so now let's take
好了，好了，现在让我们开始吧
care of the lettering in here if you
注意这里的字母，如果你
notice i have the letter s
通知我有一封信S
overlapping everything in its way let's
让我们以自己的方式重叠一切
go ahead and create that right now so
现在就去创造它吧，所以
let me grab the letter s right here
让我拿一下S这封信
let me create a duplicate of that by
让我通过以下方式创建一个副本
pressing ctrl d and i'm going to make
按下Ctrld键，我就可以
this
这
green and i'm going to give this a green
绿色，我要给这个绿色
stroke so i'm going to hold shift and
中风，所以我要按住Shift键
press on green
按下绿色按钮
again and i'm going to come over here to
再来一次，我要来这里
the fill and stroke menu
填充和描边菜单
stroke style and i'm just going to
划水风格，我要做的是
increase the size of this
增加此文件的大小
until it's as big as i need it to be
直到它大到我需要它的大小
okay so i want this to be big enough
好的，我想要这个足够大
that it's going through
它正在经历
that it's covering the tip of the letter
它盖住了信的顶端
e here
E在这里
like that but at the same time i don't
就像那样，但同时我不
want it clipping off the top of the e
想把它剪掉吗？
right here but that's okay i'll fix that
就在这里，但没关系，我会修好的
in just a minute
稍等片刻
okay so that right there is a pretty
好的，那么就在那里有一个漂亮的
good size i'm going to go to path
好尺码，我要去PATH
stroke to path object
笔划到路径对象
ungroup and then path
取消分组，然后选择路径
union and now what i will do is i will
现在我要做的是我会
i'm going to cut out this little area
我要把这一小块区域剪掉
right here that i don't want let me grab
就在这里，我不想让我抓住
the pen tool which is
钢笔工具，即
um over here the bezier pen you just
嗯，在这里，你刚刚拿到的贝塞尔钢笔
press b on the keyboard
按键盘上的b键
and i want to make sure i have the
我想要确保我有
proper mode selected which is create
选择所创建的正确模式
regular bezier path
规则Bezier路径
and i'm going to draw a shape going
我要画一个形状
through this intersecting area right
穿过这个交叉区，右转
here
这里
go back to the select tool hold shift
返回到选择工具按住Shift
click on that green letter and go to
点击绿色字母，然后转到
path
路径
difference and there we go now what i
不同的是，我们现在要做的就是
will do is i will take this green letter
我要做的就是拿着这封绿色的信
press ctrl d to duplicate it hold shift
按Ctrl d复制它，按住Shift键
click on the letter e right here and go
点击这里的字母e，然后开始
to path
至路径
oops path difference do the same thing
哦，路径差做了同样的事情
over here
在这里
duplicate it again ctrl d hold shift
再次复制ctrl d按住Shift键
click on the letter i
点击字母I
path difference and then one more time
路径差异，然后再一次
take this letter
拿着这封信
s hold shift click on this bar right
S按住Shift键右键单击此栏
here go to path
在这里转到路径
difference okay so now let's clean up
不同好的，现在让我们清理一下
this these little extra objects in here
这些额外的小物件放在这里
that we don't want
我们不想要的东西
with this object right here selected go
在此处选择此对象的情况下继续
to path break apart
将路径断开的步骤
and then we'll have everything broken up
然后我们会把一切都打碎
into individual pieces i'm going to hold
分成一个个的碎片，我要拿着
shift and click on this piece to
按住Shift键并单击此片段以
deselect it
取消选择它
then hold shift click on this piece to
然后按住Shift键单击此块以
deselect it and then the only thing left
取消选中它，然后只剩下
selected will be the objects we don't
选定的对象将是我们不选择的对象
want and then you can just press delete
想要，然后只需按Delete
on the keyboard to get rid of it
在键盘上把它去掉
and for this letter e right here i want
对于这封信，我想在这里
to get rid of this area i'm just going
为了摆脱这个地区，我正要去
to for this i'm just going to grab the
为了这个，我只是要抓住
nodes tool i'm going to go in there and
节点工具，我要进去，然后
select those nodes
选择这些节点
and then press delete on the keyboard to
然后按键盘上的Delete键以
get rid of that same thing over here
把同样的东西扔到这里去
when i get rid of this little letter
当我扔掉这封小信的时候
the tip of this little letter i press
我按下这封小信的顶端
delete there we go
删除我们开始的地方
we grab the select tool let me press one
我们抓住选择工具，让我按一下
on the keyboard to zoom out to a hundred
在键盘上缩小到100
percent
百分比
now i can click and drag over everything
现在我可以点击并拖动所有内容
come over here to the fill and stroke
到这里来填满和划水
tab
选项卡
the fill menu and bring the opacity all
填充菜单并将不透明度设置为全部
the way up to a hundred percent
通向100%的道路
and as you can see the logo is starting
如你所见，徽标正在启动
to come together it's looking pretty
走到一起它看起来很漂亮
good
好的
what i'm going to do now is i'm going to
我现在要做的是我要
add some text in here i'm going to add
在这里添加一些文本，我要添加
some more text let me grab the text tool
一些更多的文本让我抓起文本工具
let me click right there and i'm just
让我点击这里，我只是
going to write all caps
要写下所有大写字母
vintage logo so it's vintage logo
复古标志，所以这是复古标志
design let me change the text of that
设计让我改变了文字
we'll go to text
我们会去发短信
text and font and for this i'm going to
文本和字体，为此，我将
use montserrat like a bolder
像更大胆的人一样使用蒙特塞拉特
a bolder heavier weight font you can use
可以使用更粗、更粗的字体
whatever font you'd like for this any
任何您想要的字体
kind of sans font should work it doesn't
一种sans字体应该可以使用，但不能
have to be montserrat
必须是蒙特塞拉特
close out of that there we go and move
结束了，我们走了，走了
this back in a little bit
过一会儿再回来
let me grab the select tool i'm just
让我拿一下选择工具，我只是
going to put this over here towards the
我要把这个放到这边
center
中心
maybe i'll scale this down oops maybe
也许我会缩小规模，哦，也许吧
i'll scale this down a little bit
我会把这件事缩小一点
maybe i'll put some spacing between
也许我会在中间加点间距
those letters let me go back to the text
这些信件让我回到原文
tool
工具
click on the text and let me just change
点击文本，让我更改一下
the spacing to like maybe
也许是喜欢的间隔
10. see how that looks that's too much
10.看看那看起来怎么样，那太过分了
maybe seven
可能是七个
okay good enough now we'll grab the
好的，足够好了，现在我们要抓住
select tool hold shift click on the logo
选择工具按住Shift键单击徽标
there and just center it up on the
在那里，只要把它放在
vertical axis like that
像这样的垂直轴
and for this for this part you could put
对于这一部分，你可以把
whatever you want up here
你想在这里做什么都行
uh for this thumbnail design i put the
呃，对于这个缩略图设计，我把
inkscape logo up here just to show you
Inkscape徽标在这里只是为了向您展示
that this was an inkscape tutorial
这是一本Inkscape教程
but i'm just gonna for this for this
但我就是为了这件事
demonstration i'll just put some stars
演示一下，我只需要放几颗星星
in here so let me grab the stars and
在这里，所以让我抓住星星和
polygons tool
多边形工具
from the settings up here you want to
从这里的设置中，您想要
make sure you have star selected instead
请确保您选择了星形
of polygon
多边形的
five corners spoke ratio of 0.375
五角轮辐比为0.375
and then zeros for both rounded and
然后为四舍五入和
randomized now you can just go ahead and
现在随机化了，你可以继续下去了
create a star like that
创造一颗那样的明星
hold ctrl and bring your cursor up
按住Ctrl键并将光标抬起
straight up like that to create
像这样笔直地创造
a star like that now let me get rid of
像那样的明星现在让我摆脱了
the the green stroke around there by
在那里的绿色击球
holding shift and clicking on the red
按住Shift键并单击红色
x let me make this black grab the select
X让我把这件黑色的拿着精选
tool
工具
hold ctrl and shift and scale that down
按住Ctrl键和Shift键并按比例缩小
like that and put that
就像这样，把那个放在
right about there
就在那里
and then i want to make a duplicate of
然后我想复制一份
that i'm going to press ctrl d
我要按下ctrld键
then hold ctrl and move this over here
然后按住Ctrl键并将其移动到这里
like that maybe i'll make this one a
就像那样，也许我会把这件事做成
little smaller
小一点
bring that down a little bit ctrl d make
把它调低一点ctrl d make
a duplicate of that hold ctrl move that
该按住Ctrl键的副本将移动
over like that
就像那样
and then select all three of those stars
然后把这三颗星全部选中
and make sure that they're spaced apart
并确保它们是分开的
evenly come over here to the
均匀地走到这里来
align and distribute menu and we're
对齐并分发菜单，我们将
looking for a distribute right here
在这里寻找分配
and then over here where it says make
然后在这里，上面写着制造
horizontal gaps between objects equal
物体之间的水平间隙相等
click on that
点击那个
and now you can just group that all
现在您可以将所有内容分组
together by going to object
一起反对
group and then you could press you could
小组，然后你可以按你可以
hold shift on the keyboard and click
按住键盘上的换档键并单击
on the object right there and just make
放在那里的物体上，然后制作
sure you have that centered
确定你有这个中心
up like that now i'm going to go in here
就这样起来现在我要进去了
and adjust the spacing a little bit so
并稍微调整一下间距，
it looks a little more consistent maybe
看起来更一致一些也许
even make this a little bigger
甚至把这个弄大一点
press one of the keyboard to zoom back
按下其中一个键盘可回缩
out to 100 and as you can see we are
增加到100，正如你所看到的那样，我们是
done
做
so that is how you can go about creating
这就是你可以如何创建
that vintage style
那种复古风格
logo design using inkscape if you have
如果您有，请使用inkscape进行徽标设计
any questions just leave a comment below
有任何问题请在下面留下评论
and as always thanks for watching
一如既往地感谢收看
[Music]
[音乐]